eppointmentsplus.com 2019-06-13

# 

1. Privacy Overview
EppointmentsPlus, Inc. is committed to protecting the privacy of all Client and patient/end-user information.
This Privacy Statement describes Eppointments’ privacy practices.
EppointmentsPlus offers a variety of applications and services that are collectively referred to as “Services.”
Companies/medical practices (“Clients”) use Eppointments Office Scheduling as their appointment scheduling
software. EppointmentsPlus collects information from individuals who are guests and schedule with Clients’
accounts, and individuals who register and/or schedule with Clients’ accounts (“Patients” or “End-users”).
As a guest or when registering to use the Services, EppointmentsPlus requires individuals to provide the Client
with personal contact information, such as name, address, telephone number, date of birth and email address
(“Required Contact Information”).
In the event that EppointmentsPlus Client utilizes the scheduling features of the system, Client may require
their own staff to enter data into the system to facilitate use of the Services. Clients maintain a wide array of
options for what types of data may be entered concerning their Patient demographic database (i.e. names,
emails addresses, telephone numbers, account numbers, insurance information, etc). EppointmentsPlus does
not monitor the types of data required, maintained, or stored in the Services by Clients. This type of information
is referred to collectively as “Data About Patients” or “Data About Patients/End-users.”
2. Use of Information Collected
EppointmentsPlus uses Client’s Data About Patients/End-users only to perform the Services requested. Other
than the uses stated in this Statement, EppointmentsPlus does not use or share Client’s Data About for any
purpose unless required to do so by law.
The Client uses Data About Patients only to perform the Services requested. Other than the uses stated in this
Statement, EppointmentsPlus does not use or share Data About Patients/End-users for any purpose unless
required to do so by law.
Internally, EppointmentsPlus employees may be required to access Client’s Data About in order to do their
jobs. These employees are limited in number, and are committed to EppointmentsPlus privacy policies set
forth herein. All such employees execute non-disclosure agreements, which provide explicit confidentiality
protections. Any employee who violates such privacy and/or security policies is subject to possible termination
and civil and/or criminal prosecution.
The Company may use Clients for limited informational and marketing purposes about the Services. For
example, the Company may use EppointmentsPlus’s Clients to provide system updates/notices and to discuss
interest in the Services and related products and add-ons. Other than limited identification statements such as
“Scheduling by Eppointments” displayed only on the Patient/End-user self-scheduling pages and system
emails, no other type of informational or marketing communication or contact is made or displayed to
Patients/End-users.
3. Web Site Navigational Information
EppointmentsPlus uses Website Navigational Information to operate and improve the Company’s Website (i.e.
www.Eppointments.com).
EppointmentsPlus uses commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies, to collect information as
you navigate the Company’s Website (“Web Site Navigational Information”). This section describes the types
of Web Site Navigational Information that may be collected on the Company’s Website and how this
information may be used.

4. Cookies
EppointmentsPlus uses cookies to make interactions with the Company’s Web pages easy and meaningful.
When Clients and/or Patients visit the Company’s Website, EppointmentsPlus’ servers send a cookie to the
visitor’s computer. Standing alone, cookies do not personally identify an individual. Cookies merely recognize
the Web browser. Unless an individual chooses to identify himself/herself to EppointmentsPlus, such as
requesting additional information, individuals remain anonymous to the Company.
5. Sharing of Information Collected
EppointmentsPlus may share Data About Patients/End-users with other service providers to facilitate use of
the Services. For example, data center providers may be required for use of the Services. Likewise, Clients
may elect to utilize web services and integrations requiring the sharing of data to facilitate use of the Services.
EppointmentsPlus does not share, sell, rent, or trade any Client’s Data About Patients/End-user with third
parties for their promotional purposes.
EppointmentsPlus reserves the right to use or disclose information provided if required by law or if the
Company reasonably believes that use or disclosure is necessary to protect the Company’s rights and/or to
comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.
6. Security
EppointmentsPlus uses robust security measures to protect Data from unauthorized access, maintain data
accuracy, and help ensure the appropriate use of Data. When the Services are accessed using the Internet,
Transport Layer Security (TLS) technology protects Patient Data using both server authentication and data
encryption. These technologies help ensure that Patient Data is safe, secure, and only available to the Patient
to whom the information belongs and those to whom the Patient has granted access. EppointmentsPlus also
implements other advanced technology measures to prevent interference or access from outside intruders.
EppointmentsPlus offers enhanced security features within the Services that permit Clients to configure
security settings to the level they deem necessary, such as forced password. Patients are responsible for
maintaining the security and confidentiality of their EppointmentsPlus usernames and passwords.
7. Changes to this Privacy Statement
EppointmentsPlus reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement. EppointmentsPlus will provide
notification of the material changes to this Privacy Statement through the Company’s Website and/or accounts
at least thirty (30) business days prior to the change taking effect.
8. Contacting Us
Questions regarding this Privacy Statement should be directed to EppointmentsPlus Privacy by mailing to:
EppointmentsPlus, Inc., 3663 NASA Parkway 606, Seabrook, TX 77586.
